{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Chapter6Quiz.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "rug"
            ],
            "answer": "a rug",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460751.5831606,
            "question": "Given the definition \"un tappeto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ecco due famiglie"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco due famiglie.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460784.4103217,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here are two families.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "grande"
            ],
            "answer": "grande / grandi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460756.3750656,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"large (two forms)\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "your apartment"
            ],
            "answer": "your (informal) apartment",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460801.2668352,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il tuo appartamento\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ecco una famiglia"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco una famiglia.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460829.9787507,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here is a family.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "You are in a hurry"
            ],
            "answer": "You (informal) are in a hurry.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460825.402027,
            "question": "Given the definition \"(Tu) hai fretta.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "downtown",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460759.0670893,
            "question": "Given the definition \"in centro\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "hai fretta"
            ],
            "answer": "(Tu) hai fretta.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460818.0344746,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You (informal) are in a hurry.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un armadio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460913.8051205,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a closet\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Here are two families"
            ],
            "answer": "Here are two families.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460918.9212713,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco due famiglie.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a sinistra",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460888.1219554,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"on the left\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the schools",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460894.429583,
            "question": "Given the definition \"le scuole\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "big"
            ],
            "answer": "large (two forms)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460903.452968,
            "question": "Given the definition \"grande / grandi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Io ho"
            ],
            "answer": "io ho",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460880.441927,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I have\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a bed",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460920.8895998,
            "question": "Given the definition \"un letto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "small"
            ],
            "answer": "small (four forms)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460883.857257,
            "question": "Given the definition \"piccolo / piccola / piccoli / piccole\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "my house",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460967.165493,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la mia casa\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "mia casa"
            ],
            "answer": "la mia casa",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460949.5809402,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"my house\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Here is a mirror"
            ],
            "answer": "Here is a mirror.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460928.4729693,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco uno specchio.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the train station"
            ],
            "answer": "the station",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518461024.5281036,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la stazione\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ho fame"
            ],
            "answer": "(Io) ho fame.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460972.2407315,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am hungry.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ecco quattro sedie",
                "Ecco quattro sedie"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco quattro sedie.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518461018.6641507,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here are four chairs.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il tuo appartamento",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460937.9369466,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"your (informal) apartment\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Where is the station?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460976.4969807,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Dov'e' la stazione?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "in centro",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461060.6155388,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"downtown\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Here are my friends"
            ],
            "answer": "Here are my friends.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461032.186934,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco i miei amici.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "piccolo"
            ],
            "answer": "piccolo / piccola / piccoli / piccole",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461055.7715437,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"small (four forms)\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ci sono"
            ],
            "answer": "ci sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461099.2916534,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"there are\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Here are four chairs"
            ],
            "answer": "Here are four chairs.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461092.499286,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco quattro sedie.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ecco uno specchio"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco uno specchio.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518461124.6067104,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here is a mirror.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "le scuole",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461050.7563653,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the schools\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "left"
            ],
            "answer": "on the left",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461065.59934,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a sinistra\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il semaforo",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1518461239.2414467,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the traffic light\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il supermercato",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461188.1699436,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the supermarket\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un letto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461145.226605,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a bed\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am cold"
            ],
            "answer": "I am cold.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461141.3903983,
            "question": "Given the definition \"(Io) ho freddo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e un ristorante qui vicino?"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' un ristorante qui vicino?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461157.638944,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Is there a restaurant nearby?\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "an intersection",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518461225.005881,
            "question": "Given the definition \"un incorcio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la casa di Marta",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461183.5778084,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Marta's house.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Here is a family"
            ],
            "answer": "Here is a family.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461194.3697932,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco una famiglia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the supermarket",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461269.877028,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il supermercato\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "un incrocio"
            ],
            "answer": "un incorcio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461288.385219,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"an intersection\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Marta's house"
            ],
            "answer": "Marta's house.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518461321.660767,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la casa di Marta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "straight ahead",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461292.5128949,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sempre diritto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ecco i miei amici"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco i miei amici.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461316.8367553,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here are my friends.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am hungry"
            ],
            "answer": "I am hungry.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461257.7691894,
            "question": "Given the definition \"(Io) ho fame.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a closet",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461273.5339038,
            "question": "Given the definition \"un armadio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There are"
            ],
            "answer": "there are",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518461326.5645435,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ci sono\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I Have"
            ],
            "answer": "I have",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518461482.2905157,
            "question": "Given the definition \"io ho\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Is there a restaurant nearby?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518461458.9675708,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' un ristorante qui vicino?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sempre diritto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461367.9802325,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"straight ahead\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la stazione",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461363.9724858,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the station\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un tappeto",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518461475.0074432,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a rug\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ho freddo"
            ],
            "answer": "(Io) ho freddo.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518461448.5632343,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am cold.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "there is",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461379.523528,
            "question": "Given the definition \"c'e'\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "right"
            ],
            "answer": "on the right",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461423.9871562,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a destra\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the traffic light",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518461521.8872843,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il semaforo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e"
            ],
            "answer": "c'e'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461516.7585623,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"there is\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a destra",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518461512.4302216,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"on the right\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Dov'e la stazione",
                "Dov'e la stazione?"
            ],
            "answer": "Dov'e' la stazione?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518461538.1779244,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Where is the station?\"?",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}